"Sin is crouching at the door" - Genesis 4:7
The Devil's Doorway is a horror, drama film directed by Aislinn Clarke.
In the autumn of 1960, Father Thomas Riley and Father John Thornton were sent by the Vatican to investigate a
miraculous event in an Irish home for 'fallen women', only to uncover something much more horrific.
Father Thomas Riley, played by Lalor Roddy.
Father John Thornton, played by Ciaran Flynn.
Mother Superior, played by Helena Bereen.
Kathleen O'Brien, played by Lauren Coe.
Sister Maria Louise, played by Carleen Melaugh.
Eileen, played by Dearbhail Carr.
The Devil's Doorway is a 2018 found footage horror film directed by Aislinn
Clarke and co-written with Martin Brennan and Michael B.
The film had its world premiere at the 44th Seattle
International Film Festival on 25 May 2018.
IFC Midnight released the film in the United States on 13 July 2018.
The film explores themes of nun, asylum, possession, priest, possessed.
The tone is dark and emotional.